lotusjump.com 2016-10-31

# LotusJump Privacy Policy

## Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage. 

## The Information We Collect:

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the LotusJump website. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

Name   
Address   
Email address   
Phone number   
Credit/Debit Card Information   
(etc.) 

## The Way We Use Information:

We use the information you provide about yourself only to provision and maintain your account. We do not share this information with outside parties. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

## Consent To This Agreement

By using the Lotusjump site and application, you consent to the collection and use of information by Lotusjump as specified above. If we change our privacy policy, we will post changes on this page. Please check this site on a regular basis. 

## Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

## Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

## How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by going to the "my account" section of your web-based account. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

## Other content

LotusJump is not responsible for user generated content, or content found on third party websites linked-to from our site or application. 

## How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us or send us an email at support[at]lotusjump[dot]com.
